Ricketts mss. III, 1856-1979 LMC 1831
Lilly Library
- Correspondence
  - 1966 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 1968 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Undated - A-F (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Undated - G-K (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Undated - L-Q (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Undated - Goodman, Helen (Ricketts) (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Undated - King, Jasper Seymour (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Undated - King, Julia (Ricketts) (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Undated - R-Z (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Undated - Ricketts, Charles Edward (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Undated - Ricketts, Coella Lindsay (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Undated - Ricketts, Julia (Anderson) (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Undated - Ricketts, Hettie (Merriam) (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Undated - Unknown (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Financial
  - Bankbooks - C. L. Ricketts, 1899-1923 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Bankbooks - Julia Anderson Ricketts, 1908-1915 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Banking records, 1883-1893 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    Includes checks, deposit slips, foreign bank drafts, foreign exchange, loans (personal and bank), mortgages and payments
  - Banking records, 1894-1910 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Banking records, 1911-1914 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Banking records, 1915-1922 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Banking records, 1923-1925 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Banking records, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Banking records, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Banking records, 1928-1929 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Banking records, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Banking records, 1931-1932 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Banking records, 1933-1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Advertisements by CLR for "Books Wanted" (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1891-1905 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Invoices for purchases by CLR from American, English and European booksellers. Includes bills for photocopy work and orders for catalogs
  - Booksellers invoices, 1906-1907 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1908-1909 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1910-1912 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1913-1915 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1916-1919 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1920-1921 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1924-1925 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1926 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Booksellers invoices, 1931-1937 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Booksellers invoices, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Business records of the Scriptorium, 1887-1890 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    Includes purchase of materials for Scriptorium use, employee records, registered receipts for overseas mailing and insurance for mailing, subscriptions for periodicals, telephone bills, annual summaries (incomplete) of business and personal expenses (for income tax reports)
  - Business records of the Scriptorium, 1891-1894 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Business records of the Scriptorium, 1895-1899 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Business records of the Scriptorium, 1900-1905 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Business records of the Scriptorium, 1906-1907; 2 Folders (Box 13, Folder 25-26)
  - Business records of the Scriptorium, 1908-1924 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Business records of the Scriptorium, 1925-1929 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    Includes purchase of materials for Scriptorium use, employee records, registered receipts for overseas mailing and insurance for mailing, subscriptions for periodicals, telephone bills, annual summaries (incomplete) of business and personal expenses (for income tax reports). By 1925 the Business records of the Scriptorium and the Income Tax Accounts are often indistinguishable
  - Business records of the Scriptorium, 1930-1931 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Business records of the Scriptorium, 1932-1939 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Business records of the Scriptorium, 1940-1959 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Business records of the Scriptorium, 1960-1978 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Business records of the Scriptorium, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Checks payable to C. L. Ricketts, 1897-1908 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    Photocopies
  - Checks payable to C. L. Ricketts, 1909-1913 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Checks payable to C. L. Ricketts, 1914-1928 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Household receipts and personal accounts, 1885-1892 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Includes expenses for automobiles, charities, clothing, fuel, furniture, groceries, home and life insurance, music lessons, rent, travel expenses abroad, utilities. For burial expenses of Hettie (Merriam) Ricketts, see 1939, Mar. 8-May 25
  - Household receipts and personal accounts, 1893-1901 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Includes expenses for automobiles, charities, clothing, fuel, furniture, groceries, home and life insurance, music lessons, rent, travel expenses abroad, utilities
  - Household receipts and personal accounts, 1902-1905 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Household receipts and personal accounts, 1906-1908 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Household receipts and personal accounts, 1909-1910 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Household receipts and personal accounts, 1911-1915 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Household receipts and personal accounts, 1916-1925 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Household receipts and personal accounts, 1926-1929 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Household receipts and personal accounts, 1930-1933 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Household receipts and personal accounts, 1934-1936 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Household receipts and personal accounts, 1937-1945 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Includes expenses for automobiles, charities, clothing, fuel, furniture, groceries, home and life insurance, music lessons, rent, travel expenses abroad, utilities. [lb] For burial expenses of Hettie (Merriam) Ricketts, see 1939, Mar. 8-May 25
  - Household receipts and personal accounts, 1946-1947 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Household receipts and personal accounts, 1948-1949 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Household receipts and personal accounts, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Household receipts and personal accounts - England and Europe, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Household receipts and personal accounts - French, piano, and other lessons, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Income tax returns, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Julia M. Ricketts only
  - Income tax returns, 1925-1931 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Income tax returns, 1932-1936 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    1936 - gift tax return
  - Income tax returns, 1937-1952 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    1943 - checks and receipts to the IRS for settlement of CLR's estate [lb] 1945 - tax on admissions, dues, etc. [lb] 1951-1952 - quarterly reports of wages taxable under IRS
  - Invoices
    Work done by CLR and The Scriptorium as ordered; includes book and manuscript sales except for the period of 1900-1909 for which see Second-Hand Book Business folder. Arranged alphabetically by person or organization responsible for the invoice (this is largely subjective and may bear only tangential relationship)
    - A. C. Allyn and Co., 1941 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - A. G. Becker and Co., 1942-1965 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Abbots Art Gallery, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Academy of Our Lady, 1905-1926 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Ackhoff, H. W., 1915 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Acme Steel Co., 1958 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Acorn Sheet Metal Mfg. Co., 1967 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - The Active Club, 1913 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Albany Park National Bank, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Albert Pick and Co., 1919 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Alfred Adler Institute, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Allied Mills, Inc., 1941 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Alpha Kappa Phi, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - The Alumni Association, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics, 1936-1943 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - American Academy of Proctology, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - American Airlines, 1938-1941 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - American Alumni Council, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - American Association of Industrial Physicians and Surgeons, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - American Association for the Surgery of Trauma, 1939-1975 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - American Bakers Association, 1922-1957 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - American Bandmasters Association, 1942-1979 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - American Baptist Publication Society, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - American Board of Pediatrics, 1934-1969 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - American Book Company, 1913-1916 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - American Bottle Company, 1913 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - American Can Company, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - American College of Surgeons, 1913-1914 (Box 14, Folder 48)
      See also Grable's Gift and Art Galleries, 1957
    - American Conservatory of Music, 1909-1942 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - American Dental Association, 1913-1914 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - American Dietetic Association, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - American Extension University School of Law, Los Angeles and Chicago, 1913-1939 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - American Farm Bureau Federation, 1952-1965 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - American Federation of Coal Operators, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - American Field, 1918 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - American Finance Conference, 1941-1942 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - American Hospital, 1910 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - American Institute of Baking, 1922-1942 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - American Legion Posts Nos. 38, 41, and 46, 1938-1941 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - American Library Association, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - American Mathematical Society, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - American Medical Association - Women's Auxiliary, 1948-1973 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - American Missionary Association, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - American National Bank and Trust Co., 1941-1959 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - American Orthopedic Association, 1918 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - The American Power Conference, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - American Radiator Company, 1917 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - American National Red Cross - Chicago chapter, 1919-1959 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - American Roentgen Ray Society, 1920-1921 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - American Society of Animal Production / American Society of Animal Science, 1948-1976 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - American Steel Foundries, 1912-1917 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Anderson Auction Co., 1912 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Angell, William R., 1914 (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Anheuser-Busch, Inc., 1938 (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Antioch High School, Illinois, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - The Antiquarians of the Art Institute, 1905-1915 (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - Appleton Coated Paper Co., 1941 (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Armour Institute of Technology, 1897-1940 (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Arnold, John J., 1913 (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - Art Center of Chicago, 1940-1942 (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - Art Institute of Chicago, 1905-1940 (Box 14, Folder 82)
    - The Art Wall Paper Mills, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 83)
    - Arthritis Foundation, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 84)
    - Associated Colleges of Illinois, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 85)
    - Associated Jewish Charities, 1915 (Box 14, Folder 86)
    - Associated Engineers Company, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 87)
    - Austin-Cicero Manufacturers Association, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 88)
    - The Audit Company of New York, 1925 (Box 14, Folder 89)
    - Bacon, Charles S., 1915 (Box 14, Folder 90)
    - Barrington Country Day School, Illinois, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 91)
    - Barrington Public School, Illinois, 1942-1943 (Box 14, Folder 92)
    - Bastian-Blessing Co., 1941 (Box 14, Folder 93)
    - Baumgaetel, Isidor, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 94)
    - Beaver Dam, Wisconsin - Board of Education, 1908 (Box 14, Folder 95)
    - Belden Manufacturing Co., 1942-1943 (Box 14, Folder 96)
    - Berea College, 1912-1914 (Box 14, Folder 97)
    - Bernhard Quaritch, Ltd., 1923 (Box 14, Folder 98)
    - Beta Psi Fraternity, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 99)
    - Beta Theta Pi Fraternity, 1916-1960 (Box 14, Folder 100)
    - Bethel Theological Seminary, 1922-1926 (Box 14, Folder 101)
    - Beverley Country Club, 1915 (Box 14, Folder 102)
    - Binney-Galving Printing Co., 1923 (Box 14, Folder 103)
    - Blakeley Printing Co., 1938 (Box 14, Folder 104)
    - Blyth and Co., 1938 (Box 14, Folder 105)
    - Bonbright, Alice D., 1914 (Box 14, Folder 106)
      See also "Memorials, Resolutions, and Testimonials" sub-series for Mr. Crandon
    - Bonded Surveyors of America, Inc., 1940 (Box 14, Folder 107)
    - Bowers, James F., 1912-1916 (Box 14, Folder 108)
    - Bowling Alley Pin Setters, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 109)
    - Box Board Manufacturers' Association, 1916-1921 (Box 14, Folder 110)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Chicago Council, 1918 (Box 14, Folder 111)
    - Boynton, Percy H., 1925 (Box 14, Folder 112)
    - Brewster, Mrs. Walter S., 1941 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    - Briggs, E. H., 1916 (Box 14, Folder 114)
    - British Empire Association of Illinois, 1916-1942 (Box 14, Folder 115)
    - Brotherhood of Railway Trainmen, 1895 (Box 14, Folder 116)
    - Brown, Mrs. Frank E., 1912 (Box 14, Folder 117)
    - Building Managers' Association, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 118)
    - Bunnell, John A., 1916 (Box 14, Folder 119)
    - Burgess-Norton Manufacturing Co., 1945 (Box 14, Folder 120)
    - Burton, Ernest E., 1924 (Box 14, Folder 121)
    - Butler, Edward B., 1914 (Box 14, Folder 122)
    - Butler Brothers, 1914-1915 (Box 14, Folder 123)
    - Carnegie Institute, 1925 (Box 14, Folder 124)
    - Carr, Mrs. Clyde M., 1924-1925 (Box 14, Folder 125)
    - The Carr School, 1916-1921 (Box 14, Folder 126)
    - Cecilian Lyric College of Music, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 127)
    - The Central Cold Storage Co., 1941 (Box 14, Folder 128)
    - Central Guaranteed Securities Co., 1915 (Box 14, Folder 129)
    - Central Manufacturing District, 1961-1964 (Box 14, Folder 130)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 131)
    - Chas A. Stevens and Brothers, 1915-1918 (Box 14, Folder 132)
    - Chi Psi Fraternity, 1922-1961 (Box 14, Folder 133)
    - Chicago Academy of Science, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 134)
    - Chicago and Northwestern Railway, 1937-1968 (Box 14, Folder 135)
    - Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad Co., 1915-1917 (Box 14, Folder 136)
    - The Chicago Association of Commerce and Industry, 1909-1958 (Box 14, Folder 137)
    - Chicago Athletic Association, 1917-1926 (Box 14, Folder 138)
    - Chicago Auditorium Association, 1908 (Box 14, Folder 139)
    - Chicago Bar Association, 1942-1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Chicago - Board of Education/Board of Finance, 1890-1925 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Chicago - Board of Local Improvement, 1908 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Chicago - Board of Trade, 1911-1952 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Bridge and Iron Co., 1943-1952 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Chicago - Bridge Design Section, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Central Station Institute, 1914-1925 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Chicago Church Federation, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Chicago - City Council, 1896-1908 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Chicago Clearing House Association, 1911-1941 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Chicago - College of Dental Surgery, 1893 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Chicago College of Law, 1896-1897 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Chicago College of Osteopathy, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Chicago Commonwealth Club, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Chicago Corporation Counsel, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Chicago Crime Commission, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Chicago Equestrian Association, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Chicago Furniture Manufacturers Assoc., 1915 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Chicago - Grand Jury, Special, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Chicago Hardware Foundry Company, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Chicago Historical Society, 1921 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Chicago Home for Incurables, 1914-1917 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Chicago Jewelers Association, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Chicago Junction Railway Co., 1909-1914 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Chicago Kent College of Law, 1903-1944 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Chicago Latin School, 1927-1954 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, 1963-1965 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Chicago Methodist Social Union, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Chicago Midwest Credit Management Association, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Chicago Musical College, 1904 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Chicago Orphan Asylum / Chicago Child Care Society, 1914-1974 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Chicago Pathological Society, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - The Chicago Plan Commission, 1912 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - The Chicago Plan for Hospital Care, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Chicago Public Library, 1895-1966 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Chicago Railway Equipment Co., 1912-1923 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Chicago Sanitary District, 1908-1917 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Chicago Society of Ohio Women, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Chicago Stock Exchange, 1911-1923 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Chicago Surgical Society, 1937-1978 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Chicago Telephone Co., 1915 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Chicago Title and Trust Co., 1906 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Chicago Training School, 1938-1942 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Chicago Trust Co., 1925-1926 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Chicago Union Traction Co., 1908 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Chicago - Vice Commission, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Chicago Yacht Club, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Children's Memorial Hospital, 1913-1942 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Christ Church of Woodlawn, 1912 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Christensen, John C., 1923 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Christophel, D. H., 1896 (Box 15, Folder 52)
      See also - Warman, Cy, 1894
    - Church of the Holy Spirit - Lake Forest, Illinois, 1912-1940 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - City Club of Chicago, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - City National Bank and Trust Co. - Chicago, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Clan Na Gael - Hugh O'Brien Club, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Clan Na Gael - Guards, Comrades of Company B, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Clara L. Joyce Studio of Piano Music, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Clarke, Philip R., 1937 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Clearing Industrial District, Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Cleveland Kindergarten-Primary Training School, 1923-1926 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Columbia College - Chicago, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Combe Printing Co., 1916 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - The Commercial Club of Chicago, 1897-1959 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - The Commercial National Bank of St. Joseph, Michigan, 1913-1915 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Commonwealth Edison Co., 1911-1943 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Community Hospital - Geneva, Illinois, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Community House - Winnetka, Illinois, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Congregation Beth El - Chicago, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Congregation Beth El - Detroit, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Congregational Church of Evanston, Illinois, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - Conover, Charles H., 1914 (Box 15, Folder 72)
    - Consolidated Foods Corporation, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 73)
    - Container Corporation of America, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 74)
    - Continental Casualty, 1961-1966 (Box 15, Folder 75)
    - Cook County - Supt of Public Service, 1895-1908 (Box 15, Folder 76)
    - Coon, Owen L., 1941 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - Corn Exchange National Bank, 1913-1917 (Box 15, Folder 78)
    - Cornell College Alumni Association - Mt. Vernon, Iowa, 1958-1979 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    - Cosmopolitan State Bank - Chicago, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 80)
    - Cowan, Louis G., 1940 (Box 15, Folder 81)
    - Crawford State Savings Bank - Chicago, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 82)
    - Croft, F. A., 1938-1940 (Box 15, Folder 83)
    - The Crow's Nest Pass Coal Co. - St. Paul, Minnesota, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 84)
    - The Cudahy Packing Co., 1914-1921 (Box 15, Folder 85)
    - D. H. McBride and Co., 1896 (Box 15, Folder 86)
    - Danly Machine Specialties, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 87)
    - Dargan, Edwin P., 1939 (Box 15, Folder 88)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution - Illinois, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 89)
    - David, Vernon C., 1925 (Box 15, Folder 90)
    - Day, Darby A., 1911 (Box 15, Folder 91)
    - Dearborn Club - Chicago, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 92)
    - Dearborn Seminary - Chicago, 1896 (Box 15, Folder 93)
    - Detterer, E. F., 1918-1924 (Box 15, Folder 94)
    - De Wolf, Wallace L., 1917 (Box 15, Folder 95)
    - Drovers Deposit National Bank / Drovers National Bank, 1909-1957 (Box 15, Folder 96)
    - Drucker, Mrs. Henry W., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 97)
    - Duncan Electric Co., 1912-1965 (Box 15, Folder 98)
    - Dundee Community High School - Illinois, 1940-1941 (Box 15, Folder 99)
    - Edgewater Golf Club, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 100)
    - Ela Township Republican Men's Club, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 101)
    - The Eleanor Association, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 102)
    - Elizabeth McCormick Memorial Fund, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 103)
    - Elizabethtown, Kentucky - Schools, 1900 (Box 15, Folder 104)
    - The Elliot Company, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 105)
    - Elmhurst College, 1939-1942 (Box 15, Folder 106)
    - Elm Place School - Highland Park, Illinois, 1938-1942 (Box 15, Folder 107)
    - Emmanuel Church of La Grange, Illinois, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 108)
    - Evangelical Theological Seminary, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 109)
    - Evangelical United Brethren Church - Board of Bishops, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 110)
    - Evanston Hospital Association, 1914-1965 (Box 15, Folder 111)
    - Evanston Public Library, 1925-1937 (Box 15, Folder 112)
    - Evanston Public Schools - Illinois, 1911-1920 (Box 15, Folder 113)
    - Evanston Woman's Club, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 114)
    - Exmoor Country Club - Highland Park, Illinois, 1938-1939 (Box 15, Folder 115)
    - Fabyan, George, 1916-1917 (Box 15, Folder 116)
    - The Fairies Riding School, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 117)
    - The Faulkner School, 1912-1969 (Box 15, Folder 118)
    - Federal Electric Company, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 119)
    - Federal Reserve System - Federal Advisory Council, 1938-1957 (Box 15, Folder 120)
    - Federal Sign System, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 121)
    - Fender, Mrs. E. E., 1940 (Box 15, Folder 122)
    - Field Museum of Natural History, 1912-1921 (Box 15, Folder 123)
    - Findley, A. Ray, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 124)
    - Firman House, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 125)
    - First Illinois Infantry, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 126)
    - First National Bank - Chicago, 1907-1959 (Box 15, Folder 127)
    - First National Bank - Elgin, Illinois, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 128)
    - First National Bank - Lake Forest, Illinois, 1954-1958 (Box 15, Folder 129)
    - First National Bank - Oaklawn, Illinois, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 130)
    - First National Bank - St. Paul, Minnesota, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 131)
    - First National Bank - Winnetka, Illinois, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 132)
    - First Presbyterian Church of Chicago, 1911 (Box 15, Folder 133)
    - First State Pawners Society - Chicago, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 134)
    - Flossmoor Country Club - Chicago, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 135)
    - Food Equipment Manufacturing Co., 1965 (Box 15, Folder 136)
    - Foote Bros. Gear and Machinery Corp., 1939 (Box 15, Folder 137)
    - The Foreign Newspaper Publishers of Chicago, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 138)
    - The Forty Club, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 139)
    - The Frances Shimer School - Mt. Carroll, Illinois, 1908-1926 (Box 15, Folder 140)
    - Francis W. Parker School - Chicago, 1912-1942 (Box 15, Folder 141)